

# Jovita Morkūnė Quality Assurance Specialist

- +370 636 58227
- jovita.morkune@gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/jovita-morkune/
- Kaunas, Lithuania

#### SUMMARY

I am responsible, diligent, attentive and have good interpersonal skills. I am used to an agile work environment and can quickly adapt to changing business requirements.

Over the past 5 years, I had an opportunity to work with culturally diverse teams, where I was focusing on ensuring a high level of quality in the work my team was doing.

Currently, I'm studying a lot to become a software QA engineer. I would love to join a software company where I could create value by contributing to the quality assurance of interesting software products while also gaining more practical experience.

#### EXPERIENCE

# **Sourcery for Testers Student**

07/2020 - Present

Devbridge

# **Quality Improvement Specialist**

03/2016 - 02/2020

R1 RCM

- · Conducted monthly process reviews for each team member per the quality assurance review procedures.
- Ensured the high-quality work of my team specialists.
- Investigated trends, analyzed root causes of rejected claims, and proposed solutions to resolve any concerns.
- · Prepared and leaded training of new and existing staff.
- Improved processes with macro commands to increase productivity and to avoid repetitive errors.
- · Initiated additional projects with other teams, which helped to generate more income for the company.

# **Account Resolution Specialist**

05/2015 - 03/2016

Intermedix

- Identified reasons for denied insurance claims and effectively resolved them by determining a course of action in the revenue cycle management process.
- Made calls to insurance companies when needed.
- Maintained high productivity and work quality results.
- Worked on various projects, collaborated with team members to reach the team goals.

#### EDUCATION

International Business 2018

Kaunas University of Technology - Master's degree

Finance 2015

Kaunas University of Technology - Bachelor's degree

# CERTIFICATES

End to End Testing with Cypress: CodeMash (Pluralsight)

04/2020 - Present

JavaScript Essential Training (LinkedIn)

04/2020 - Present

Learning SQL Programming (LinkedIn)				
End-to-End JavaScript Testing with Cypress.io (LinkedIn)				
Programming Foundations: Software Testing/QA (LinkedIn)				
The Web Developer Bootcamp (Udemy)				
Global Collaboration Certificate (X-Culture)				
SKILLS				
Teamwork	Expert	JavaScript	Beginner	
Quality Assurance	Advanced	HTML/CSS	Beginner	
Analytical Skills	Advanced	MongoDB	Beginner	
JIRA	Intermediate	Postman API	Beginner	
LANGUAGES				
English	Intermediate	Lithuanian	Native	

Russian

Basic